multiplayer.com 2004-04-02

# Multiplayer.com

|   
---  
  
There are currently, 22 guest(s) and 0 member(s) that are online.

You are Anonymous user. You can register for free by clicking here  

---  

**  
Multiplayer.com Privacy Policy**

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

 ****

****
  * This Privacy Policy covers Multiplayer.com’s treatment of personally identifiable information that Multiplayer.com collects when you are on the Multiplayer.com site, and when you use Multiplayer MGOLD service.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Multiplayer.com does not own or control, or to people that Multiplayer.com does not employ or manage.

**

Information Collection and Use

**

****
  * Multiplayer.com collects personally identifiable information when you register for the Multiplayer MGOLD Subscription Service. Multiplayer.com does not receive personally identifiable information from our business partners or network properties.
  * When you register with Multiplayer MGOLD , our payment processing partner will ask for your name, email address and billing address. Once you register with Multiplayer MGOLD and sign in to our service, you are not completely anonymous to us. 
  * Multiplayer.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Multiplayer.com cookie information and the page you requested.
  * Multiplayer.com uses personal information for two general purposes: to process subscription payments and to contact you about promotions and additions to our service.

**

Information Sharing and Disclosure

**

****
  * Multiplayer.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.
  * Multiplayer.com may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:
    * We have your consent to share the information;
    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Multiplayer.com to provide our service to you. (such as our payment processing company);
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
    * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Multiplayer.com Terms of Service.

**

Cookies

**

****
  * Multiplayer.com may set and access Multiplayer.com cookies on your computer.
  * Multiplayer.com allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Multiplayer.com's cookies.

**

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

**

****
  * Multiplayer.com gives you the ability to edit your Multiplayer.com Account Information at any time.
  * You may request cancellation of your Multiplayer.com account by logging into your PayPal account and going to the "History" subtab of the "My Account" tab. Choose "Subscriptions" from the pull-down "Show" menu and press the "Submit" button. Choose this subscription, and click on its "Status." You will be taken to a Transaction Details page from which you may cancel your subscription. Canceling your subscription will immediately stop all future scheduled payments for the subscription.

**

Security

**

****
  * Your Multiplayer.com Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.
  * In certain areas Multiplayer.com uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

**

Changes to this Privacy Policy

**

****
  * Multiplayer.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

**

Questions or Suggestions

**

****
  * If you have questions or suggestions please  forward them to us.

| 

|   
---  
  
---  
[ASTROBATTLE](http://www.multiplayergamepass.com/abPortal.asp) is a multiplayer network space simulation where you design, program and pilot your own space craft against online opponents.   

[Territories 3069](http://www.multiplayergamepass.com/territoriesPortal.asp) is a multi-user, graphical turn-based strategy game where players compete against one another to rule the known universe. Players must gather and manage resources, plan and execute attacks with large fleets of ships and defend their own galaxies.  
  
Sign up right now for a 7 day trial with unlimited access to **AstroBattle** and **Territories 3069** \- plus a dozen more of the hottest independent online multiplayer games for just 

**$3.75**.
